// creating an array and passing the number, questions, options,and answers
let questions3 = [
    {
        numb: 1,
        question: "Which of the following class Styles a table with a light gray background to rows while the cursor hovers over them?",
        answer: ".table-hover",
        options: [
            ".table",
            ".table-striped",
            ".table-bordered",
            ".table-hover"

        ]
    },

    {
        numb: 2,
        question: "Sytle of Button represents a contextual button for informational alert messages?",
        answer: ".btn-info",
        options: [
            ".btn",
            ".btn-primary",
            ".btn-success",
            ".btn-info"

        ]
    },

    {
        numb: 3,
        question: "Sytle of button makes the button size large",
        answer: ".btn-lg",
        options: [
            ".btn-lg",
            ".btn-sm",
            ".btn-xs",
            ".btn-block"

        ]
    },

    {
        numb: 4,
        question: "Styles are used to add a dropdown to a tab?",
        answer: ".nav,.nav-tabs,dropdown-.menu",
        options: [
            ".nav,.nav-tabs,.menu",
            ".nav,.nav-tabs,dropdown-.menu",
            ".nav,.nav-pills,.dropdown",
            ".nav,.nav-pills"

        ]
    },

    {
        numb: 5,
        question: "Which of the following is correct about modal plugin?",
        answer: "Both of the above",
        options: [
            "you can toggle the modal plugin's hidden content via data attributes",
            "you can toggle the modal plugin's hidden content via javascript",
            "Both of the above",
            "None of the above"

        ]
    },

    {
        numb: 6,
        question: "Which of the following is correct about data-html Data attribute of Tooltip Plugin",
        answer: "if false,jQuery's Text method will be used into the dom",
        options: [
            "applies a CSS fade transition to the tooltip",
            "Specifies how to position the tooltip",
            "if false,jQuery's Text method will be used into the dom",
            "Delegates to the specifies targets"

        ]
    },

    {
        numb: 7,
        question: "Data-animation Data attributes of Popover plugin?",
        answer: "Applies a Css Fade transition to the popover",
        options: [
            "Delegates to the specified targets",
            "None of them",
            "Applies a Css Fade transition to the popover",
            "A & B"

        ]
    },

    {
        numb: 8,
        question: "Which of the following is correct about Bootstrap",
        answer: "All of the above",
        options: [
            "EAsier web Development",
            "it uses HTML, CSS and JavaScript",
            "BootStrap was developed by mark Otto",
            "All of the above"

        ]
    },


    {
        numb: 9,
        question: "if you want to create an inverted .navbar with a black background and with white text?",
        answer: ".navbar-inverse",
        options: [
            ".navbar-inverse",
            ".navbar-reverse",
            ".navbar-inverted",
            "None of the above"

        ]
    },

    {
        numb: 10,
        question: "Style can be used to create progress bars with different styles?",
        answer: ".progress-bar-success, -info,-warining,-dangger",
        options: [
            ".progress-bar-success, -info,-warining,-dangger",
            ".success,.info,.warning,.danger",
            ".progress,.progress-bar",
            "None of the above"

        ]
    }

]
